It's cold.
寒いね
I want a muffler.
マフラーが欲しいね
Her new hairstyle is so cute.
髪型変わってすごい可愛い
Yay!
やったー
bangs.
前髪
That too.
それもね
I bought Pop'n.
ポップン買ったね
Salty, salted buttery.
塩味、塩バター味
It smells so good and looks delicious.
いい匂いめっちゃ美味しそう
Are you going to eat all of that by yourself?
それ全部一人食べるんでしょ?
You can eat it.
食べれるよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
There's quite a lot though.
結構量あるけどね
I'm looking forward to the movie.
映画楽しみだね
Shall we go?
行こうか
It's Hawaii.
ハワイですね
you.
君
What did you think of the Asaki-chan movie?
アサキちゃん映画どうだった?
It was fun.
楽しかったね
It was really interesting.
めっちゃ面白かったな
It was very impressive.
迫力満点だった
I'm happy to have a cute date in a fashionable place.
オシャレなとこで 可愛くデートして 僕幸せですわ
good.
よかった
I had fun too.
私も楽しかったです
I'll be back again.
また来るよね
Let's go.
行こうね
Isn't it a little short?
少し短くない?
I saw it.
見てしまいました
I was seen.
見られちゃった
It's cold.
寒いね
The illumination is so beautiful.
イルミネーションすごく綺麗だね
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
You like glitter, right?
キラキラ好きでしょ?
I love it.
大好きです
What else do you want to do in winter?
あと冬は何したいことあるの?
I want to take a hot spring bath.
温泉入りたいです
I like hot springs.
温泉好きなんだ
Which hot spring do you like?
どこの温泉が好きなんだ?
I don't know.
わかんない
I haven't been there much.
あんまり行ったことないです
Have you never been there?
行ったことないんだ?
Well then, I'll take you with me next time.
じゃあ今度俺が連れてやろうか
Yay!
やったー
He also plays the role of a date.
またデートの役をする
happy.
嬉しい
I'll buy you popcorn then too.
その時もポップコーン買ってあげるね
Is there any popcorn?
ポップコーンあるかな?
There may not be a hot spring.
温泉ないかも
I have no choice but to buy it at a convenience store.
コンビニで買うしかない
Asaki-chan looks good on Rokuhon.
アサキちゃん六本に似合うね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
happy.
嬉しい
You don't usually come here, right?
普段あんまり来ないでしょ?
It's not coming.
来ないです
It feels special.
特別な感じします
It's special.
特別だね
Asaki-chan.
アサキちゃん
yes.
はい
long time no see.
久しぶり
How have you been?
元気だった?
I'm fine.
元気です
You look cute today too.
今日もかわいいね
I enjoyed the movie earlier.
さっき映画楽しかったね
it was fun.
楽しかった
The popcorn was good, right?
ポップコーンうまかったでしょ?
It was delicious.
美味しかった
He said it was delicious.
美味しいって言ってたもんな
How have you been lately?
元気だった最近は?
I was fine.
元気でしたよ
Tell me what you enjoyed recently.
最近楽しかったこと教えて
What is it?
何だろう?
some time ago.
さっき
What was the most fun you had just now?
さっき一番楽しかったか?
it was fun.
楽しかった
It was beautiful, the illumination.
綺麗だったしね、イルミネーションね
It was the first time this year.
今年初でした
Was it your first time this year?
今年初だった?
I see.
そうか
Haven't you been playing with boys lately?
最近男の子と遊んでないんですか?
not at all.
全然
Haven't you played at all?
全然遊んでない?
It's a waste, it's so cute.
もったいないじゃん、こんなかわいいの
is that so?
そうですか?
Why don't you play?
なんで遊ばない?
There is no other person.
相手がいない
Is that so?
そうなの?
That's right.
そうなんだ
That's too much to choose from.
選びすぎだな、それは
No, no.
違う、違う
It's so cute.
こんなかわいいんだよ
Isn't your skin getting whiter every night?
毎夜肌白くなってない?
that's right.
そうです
Try standing up once.
一回立ってみて
What do you do for Christmas?
クリスマス何する?
I haven't done it.
やってないです
Haven't you done it?
やってないの?
Then at home?
じゃあお家で?
Have you finished watching the movie?
映画見て終わりか
Watch Demon Slayer Eva Netlix.
鬼滅のエヴァのネットリックス見て
Why Demon Slayer?
なんで鬼滅?
Because you look like you like me.
好きそうな顔をしてるから
I haven't seen the new one yet.
新しいのまだ見てないよ
Did you see the previous one?
前のやつ見た?
I saw it all.
全部見ました
Look behind you.
後ろ見てごらん
Twintel looks good on you.
ツインテル似合うね
It looks great on you.
すごい似合う
Try rolling up your skirt a little.
スカートちょっと巻いてみて
It's interesting.
面白いんだよな
Show me more of everything.
もっと全部見せて
She's wearing something super naughty underneath.
すごいエッチな下に履いてるじゃん
That's what I wear.
そんなもん履くんだ
Have you gotten fired up?
気合入れてきた?
Do you like seeing guys' faces when they're feeling good?
アタシちゃんさ、 男の人の 気持ちよくなってる顔見るの好き?
I might like it.
好きかも
Maybe you like it?
好 きかも?
Have you never been very sexually active?
エッチとかさ、あんまり攻めたことないの?
From myself.
自分から
Not much.
あんまり
There isn't.
ないんだ
Furu-chan likes being attacked, right?
フルちゃん攻められるの好きだよね?
really like.
大好き
He says he loves it.
大好きだって
Today, I'd like to ask you to attack me a little.
今日、 ア タシちゃんにちょっと攻めてもらおうか
yes.
はい
Challenge.
チャレンジ
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Can such a cute girl attack?
こんな可愛い子が 攻めれるかな?
Properly.
ちゃんと
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Try your best.
頑張ってみて
One more time.
もう一回
Oh, nice.
ああ、いいな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Kuro-chan, come forward.
黒ちゃん、前を
Kuro-chan's ears are made to stick out.
黒ちゃん、耳出る仕様になってる
Have you ever licked a man's ear?
男の人の耳舐めたことある?
There are no women.
女の人ない
do not have?
ない?
Kuro-chan, please chew my ears.
黒ちゃんがさ、耳、 チューして
Everyone is such a cute girl.
みんなこんな可愛い子に
It's me, please take it easy on me.
アタシちゃんさ、 軽くベロで
Eat my ears.
耳食べて
Eat it all.
全部 食べて
around you.
周りで
You're really good at licking, aren't you?
ア タ シ ちゃん、 めっちゃ舐め方できるじゃん
Is it done?
できてる?
You're doing your best.
頑張ってるね
He's trying to be wild.
すごい野良しようとしてる
Deep inside your ears, up to this point.
耳の奥のさ、 このとこまで
Try putting it all in?
いっぱい入れてみ?
I put it in my ear.
耳口の中に入れちゃって
copper?
どう?
I started to feel a lot of men.
男の人いっぱい感じだせちゃって
How do you feel?
どんな気分?
I'm a little excited.
ちょっと興奮する
Are you getting a little excited?
ちょっと興奮しちゃう?
It's cute.
可愛いね
Opposite ear.
反対の耳
It's a crackling sound.
ピチャピチャ音だって
It's like I'm chewing something naughty.
なんか、 えっちなチューしてるみたいな
What does it taste like?
どんな味する?
I can't hear it.
耳わかんない
The taste of the ears.
耳の味
The one I don't understand.
わかんないやつ
Chew, chu.
チューか、チュー
I'll have a lot of fun there.
いっぱいそこにチューしちゃいな
Kuru-chan, you're happy.
くるちゃん、 幸せだね
It's a great house.
すごいうちだよ
Stick out your tongue and say slowly.
舌出して、 ゆっくりベローンって
I'm going to lick it all off with my head.
頭で全部舐めちゃう
It was called bellow bellow, so there are a lot of bellows.
ベローベローってしたから、 ベローンっていっぱいな
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
I want to wear a lot of bellows.
いっぱいベローつけたい
Close
く る
chan, does it come with it?
ちゃん、 そう付属する?
amazing.
すごい
I'm so happy to have such cute hair.
幸せだな、こんな可愛い髪
It's a lot of bellow bellowing.
いっぱいベローベローしてる
It's like this.
こんな感じです
You were good at licking.
舐めるの上手かったね
Amazing chan.
すごいちゃん
Shackle.
しくび
Slowly lick from the chew.
チューからゆっくり舐める
slowly.
ゆっくり
Chu
チュ
- It stopped all the time.
ー でずっと止まって
I licked it, so I licked it.
舐めたからベロベロして
Be gentle and slow.
優しくゆっくり
Please lick it more.
もっといっぱいベロベロして
Take your tongue out.
ベ ロ出して
I made a big splash.
ちくびビンビンにしたね
Chikku taste.
ちくびの味
Do something?
何かする?
Chikku taste.
ちくびの味
Didn't you?
しなかった?
I don't know.
わかんない
I didn't understand.
わからなかった
Chikubisa on the other side.
反対側のちくびさ
Inhale this at once.
もう一気に吸ってこれ
Lick it all into your mouth.
全部口に舐める
Spin around and around
ちくびに回りぐるんぐる
yeah.
ん
It might feel good.
気 持ちいいかも
Feels good.
気持ちいい
What about a man's lips?
男の人のちくびどうだ?
I'm glad you're feeling better.
気持ちよくなってくれてるの嬉しい
Were you happy?
嬉しかった?
So cute.
可愛いな
Do you know?
知ってる?
Men know what feels best, right?
男 の人は一番気持ちよく知ってるでしょ?
Do you know?
知ってる?
Can you tell me?
言ってみ?
where?
どこ?
What's your name?
名前なんて言う?
名前なんて?
Do you want me to tell you?
言ってもらう?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
You want to see it, right?
見たくなっちゃったでしょ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Have them lower you slowly.
ゆっくり下ろしてもらう
Positive.
前向き
There's a chinch.
チンチあるね
It's twitching.
ピクピク動いてるね
I just happened to fit it in.
たまたま収まってあげて
I happened to hold it in my hand.
たまたま手で握ってね
How do you feel when you see Chinch?
チンチ見るとどういう気分になる?
It feels strange.
不思議な感じ
I get a little excited.
ちょっと興奮しちゃう
Shall we do it?
しちゃう?
Chinch Chinch.
チ ンチ
Have them move slowly.
ゆっくり動かしてもらう
You're looking amazing.
すごいチンチ見てるね
I touched my tip.
さきっぽを触ったの
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいって
That was good.
良かったね
I'll keep an eye on Sakipo too.
さきっぽも注視やる
I'll keep an eye on everything.
全部注視やる
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I happened to perot all the way to the top.
た またま上までペローって
It's bigger than my face.
顔より大きくなっちゃったね
It's Sakippo Perot.
さきっぽペローって
Very good.
すごい良い
Then, gulp slowly.
そ したら ゆっくりガブって
Are you happy that Chinch has grown so big?
チンチこんなに大きくなって嬉しい?
happy.
嬉しい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
happy.
嬉しい
Sit down.
座って
I'm going to close my mouth.
さきっぽを締めちゃう
It feels good to be a man, so please tighten it as much as possible.
男の人、さきっぽ気持ちいいから いっぱい締めてもらう
Tighten the opening with your hands.
手でさきっぽをいっぱい締めて
that's right.
そうです
In addition, I want to feel good with my mouth.
加えて 口でいっぱい気持ちよくしたい
Violently.
激しく
Everything.
全部じゃん
Have the roots inserted at the same time.
根元も同時に入れてもらう
Fill your mouth with dick.
口の中、チンチンでいっぱいにして
Make more noise.
もっと音立ててもらう
Why not add it to the limit first?
最初に限界まで加えない?
I find it painful.
苦しいと思ってしまう
My mouth is full of dick and I have to hit it.
口の中、チンチンでいっぱいになって 打ちなきゃならないで
Sho.
しょ
I'll tighten it as much as possible.
い っぱい締めてあげる
fun?
楽しい?
It sounds like it feels really good.
すごい気持ちよさそうな音してる
One more lick from below.
下からもう一回ベロベロ
I haven't covered everything.
全部舐めてないところね
Lick it all
全部舐めて
give.
あ げる
I'll lick it all.
全部 舐めてあげる
More will fit there.
そっちはもっと入る
One more time.
もう一回
Masaki's face is full of color.
まさきちゃんの顔色でいっぱい
One more time to the very end.
最後一番奥までもう一回
Just talk about it.
じぼうじぼうしゃべってほら
Go out to Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃんにつきだして
It turned out like this.
こんなになっちゃったよ
happy?
嬉しい?
Masaki-chan is so cute that I cut her like this.
まさきちゃん可愛いからこんなの切ったな
Shall we tease you a little more in bed?
ベッドでもうちょっといじめちゃおうか
Well then, let's move to the bed next.
じゃあさ、 次にベッド移動しよっか
Kuro-chan, head over here.
黒ちゃん、こっち頭
Bring your face closer.
チンチン顔近づけて
Use your mouth and hands too.
口と手も使って
Like before.
さっきっぽい
Just tease me.
いじめてほら
Make a hedging sound.
ヘッジな音出して
Ippa
いっぱ
stomach.
い
Look at Chinch.
チ ンチ見てほら
If you want to lick it, you can lick it a lot.
舐めたかったり、いっぱい舐めてもいいんだよ
I want to do lots of things to make you feel good.
い っぱいいろんなことして、 気持ちよくしたいな
You feel amazing, Kuro-chan.
すごい感じてるよね、黒ちゃん
Lick it all from the bottom.
下からペロリ全部舐めてほら
It's a hedge.
きしとチンチン、ヘッジだね
Let's lick it so much that I can't hold back.
我慢できないぐらい、いっぱい舐めちゃおう
The whole thing is licked into the mouth.
全部口に舐められる
hard.
硬い
Do it as quickly as possible.
それを思いっきり早く
Come on, come on.
さあさあ、
Go back.
戻 って
I don't bully.
いじめない
Express your feelings a lot.
いっぱい気持ちを出す
stomach
い
I don't get bored.
じ めない
Don't get bullied.
い じめない
It's fun to squeeze your dick, isn't it?
チンチンしめるの楽しいでしょ?
So, I returned it and lo and behold.
で、返し上がってほら
Squeeze out the spirit.
精神絞り取ってほら
Kiri-chan, is it delicious?
きりちゃん、おいしい?
delicious.
おいしい
Well then, let's do something we've never done to Asahi-chan.
じゃあ、もっとさ、 あさひちゃんにやったことないことしちゃお
I guess.
う かな
You want to lick all kinds of men, right?
男のいろんな人とか舐めてみたいでしょ?
Black-chan, raise your legs.
黒ちゃん、足を上げてほら
Butt.
お尻
What can happen?
なんてことある?
do not have?
ない?
Shall we try licking it for the first time?
初めて舐めてみるか?
Would you like to try it?
やってみる?
The blood on my butt.
お尻のところの血を
copper?
どう?
Does it feel like pouring it into your butthole?
お尻の穴に注した感じ?
It feels weird.
変な感じ
You're doing something really weird.
めっちゃなことしてるんですよね
One more time.
もう 一回
I kept pouring it all the time.
ずっと注したまま
Slowly reach out from below.
下からゆっくり手を伸ばして
I licked your asshole.
お尻の穴を舐めちゃったね
As for the man.
男の人は
Suck it and see.
吸ってほら
From the ass hole to the tip of the penis.
お尻の穴からチンチンの先まで
If you go from the butt to the tip, start talking.
お尻から先っぽまで行ったら、 チ ンチン喋ってほ
and others.
ら
The current tongue.
今 のベロベロ
My butt is swollen.
お尻がベロベロしてる
Looks really fast.
すごい速そう
Use it deeper into your tongue.
もっとベロの奥まで使って
All stuck in the holes.
全部穴にくっついて
While touching his penis with that hand.
その手でチンチン触りながら
Lick while teasing.
いじめながら舐める
Look at Chin Chin too.
チンチンもほら
Chin Chin is also funny.
チンチンもおかしながら
that's right.
そうです
Lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐める
Lick it harder.
もっと激しく舐めてほら
Push it into the tongue hole.
ベロ穴に突っ込んで
So take out your dick and see.
それでチンチンを出してほら
But this was my first experience with a man's butthole.
でも男の人の お尻の穴は 初めての経験したね
Finally, tease it clearly and quickly.
最後にそれをもっきり 速くいじめて
Ching Chin.
チンチン
It felt so good.
すごい気持ちよくきた
Bring more.
もっと持ってこら
Have fun.
楽しね
Kuro-chan.
クロちゃん
I'm starting to feel like bullying her.
そろそろいじめたくなってきた
Kuro-chan too.
ク ロちゃんも
I want to give it back.
やり返したいな
やり返したいよね
I want it back.
やり返したいって
やり返したいんだって
Asahi-chan, let's take a look at her pussy too.
あさひちゃんも マンコ見よっかな
Come here.
こっちおいで
Let's both go deeper.
もっと二人とも 一番奥まで入れて
Lick each other a lot.
いっぱい舐め合いな
Asahi-chan, cute ears.
あさひちゃん、かわいいお耳
Kuro-chan, this.
クロちゃん、これ
Lick it.
舐めちゃえ
Look.
見て
Do you like listening?
耳好きなの?
like.
好き
Get licked and show me a lot.
舐められていって、いっぱい見せてくれ
Do you get wet when your fingers are licked?
指舐められて濡れちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it a long time since I've seen a pussy?
マンコ、久々じゃない?
This is also the shape of my feet.
足の形もこんなもん
You're fidgeting.
もじもじしちゃってるじゃん
Kuro-chan, please lick the inside of my hole.
クロちゃん、穴の中まで舐めてくれ
I can really feel it.
ほんに感じちゃうね
Kuro-chan, please lick my neck too.
クロちゃん、首も舐めてくれ
Can you lick my neck?
首舐められる?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Asahi-chan, you're a pervert.
あさひちゃん、変態だね
That's a pervert.
変態だね
Listen one last time.
最後はもう一回耳
You like ears, right?
耳好きでしょ?
You want me to lick you, right?
舐めて欲しいでしょ?
You licked it.
舐めたね
Then I licked it upwards.
そしたら上へ舐めました
hey.
ね
Ah, Sahi-chan, you love your ears.
あ さひちゃん、耳大好きなんだね
That was a naughty reaction.
エッチな反応してたね
Her skin is still pure white.
相変わらず真っ白な肌だね
It's so white.
すごい白いね
Kuro-chan, slowly turn your shoulders towards the earth.
クロちゃん、ゆっくり肩を地球にして
beautiful.
綺麗
Asahi-chan is really beautiful.
あさひちゃん、ほんと綺麗だよね
Look, like this
ほら、こんな
color.
色
What's the opposite?
反 対は?
You're so naughty.
すっごいエッチなっぱいしてるね
It's soft.
柔らかいね
The shape is also very beautiful.
形もすごい綺麗
So cute, what is this?
かわいい、これなんちゃう?
Belovero.
ベロベロって
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
Stand up full of chikubi.
チクビいっぱい立たせて
How does it feel to have your breasts licked?
おっぱい舐められてどう?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It might feel good and it might be cute.
気持ちいいかもかわいいね
Kuro-chan, put all your breasts in your mouth.
クロちゃん、おっぱい全部口の中に入れちゃえ
Talk to me about your breasts.
お っぱ い喋っちゃえ
I'll be licked.
舐められちゃう
Sit down with your breasts.
お っぱ いすっちゃえ
Let's take a look.
チクビ見してみよう
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Shut up your boobs.
おっぱいすっちゃえ
Get rid of both.
両方すっちゃえ
Do you like being licked?
舐められるの好きなの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I love being licked.
舐められるの大好きだね
Japanese girls also like being licked, right?
日本の子も舐められるの好きでしょ?
Drink your feet.
足飲みてごらん
Kuro-chan, please dye your pants.
ク ロ ちゃん、パンツを染めてごらん
copper?
どう?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's so naughty.
すごいエッチだよ
I can see it a little bit.
なんかちょっと見えちゃってる
Kuro-chan, shift that.
クロちゃん、それずらして
My boobs and ears were licked.
おっぱいと耳舐められちゃった
I got wet.
濡れちゃったんだ
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Look at that.
それを見て
I got bored
くり立っちゃった
I did.
んだ
Kuro-chan took off his pants.
ク ロちゃん、パンツを脱がした
Push your butt forward more.
もっとお尻前に突き出して
Are you often drawn to the back?
後ろによくかかれる?
Hand to yourself.
自分に手で
more.
もっと
I'm in trouble now.
もう困るね
Look down to your butt hole.
お尻の穴までほら
Then spread the sides of your pussy as wide as you can.
そしたらマンコの 横をもっと思いっきり広げて
Show me everything inside.
中に全部見せて
Kuro-chan, Biller.
クロちゃん、ビラー
Use it all.
全部使い込んでほら
Just put it all down.
全部置いてほら
Looks good.
よく見える
It's wet inside too.
中も濡れてるね
It's closed.
閉めてるよ
Kuro-chan, Kuritate, touch me.
クロちゃん、くり立、触って
You like that, don't you?
そこ好きでしょ?
Add ivy and rub it.
ツタつけてくりこすって
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだよ
Was it close to being toyed with?
くりいじられてると近くてたのか
You're becoming more and more lonely.
どんどん孤独になってくるね
what happened?
どうしたの?
cute face
可愛い顔が
be.
ある
Make sure it's warm inside.
そ ん中温かいか確かめてほら
I'll put it in.
入れるよ
slowly.
ゆっくり
Inside the pussy.
マンコの中
warm.
温かい
That's amazing.
すごいね
It makes a sound.
音するよ
It's very wet inside.
中まですごい濡れてるね
Add more tongue.
もっとベロつけて
To the back.
奥 まで
It has amazing stripes.
すごい縞あるね
Show me the hole you pulled out.
抜いた穴を見せて
It's wide all the way to the back.
奥まで広いね
Very deep.
すっごい奥まで
One more time.
もう一回
Just lick it.
ちょっとさ、舐めてほら
I'm really licking it.
すっごい舐めてるよ
Close
く る
Let's suck it up completely.
と りをすっかり吸ってあげてほら
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Give me more tongue.
もっとベロを出して
Lick it all from below.
下から全部舐めてあげてほら
It seems to be coming from the corner of the pussy.
マンコの隅からすんばりそう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's got a great sound.
すごい音になってるね
It's wet.
びちゃびちゃね
It's making a naughty sound.
エッチな音してるよ
It seems to be coming from the corner of the pussy.
マンコの隅からすんばりそう
The corner of the pussy is covered
マ ン コ の 隅 からすん
Looks like it.
ば りそう
Looks amazing.
す ん ばりそう
It looks like it's coming from the corner of my pussy.
マ ンコの隅からすんばりそう
Do you look comfortable?
気持ちいい顔してる?
Kuru-chan.
くるちゃん
I was able to stay in the hole for a while.
穴の中にしばんくらいしちゃいけたよ
That's cool.
すっこい
It was full earlier.
もっと早くいっぱいいたよ
Do you know what's in there?
入ってるの分かる?
I understand.
分かる
I know it's in there.
入ってるの分かる
terrible.
やばい
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
That's what I said.
こう いうことしたよ
Kuru-chan,
くるちゃん、
Show me your dripping wet pussy once.
び しょびしょのおまんこ一回見せてほら
Spread it out as much as you can.
思いっきり広げてほら
More to the limit.
もっと限界まで
The farthest side is visible.
一番奥目のほうが映ってるよ
Furi hora.
ふりほら
Here's a naughty pussy.
エッチなおまんこほら
Kuru-chan,
く る ちゃん、
Put your finger in.
指 入れてさ
It felt good up there.
上の気持ちいいとこしたのね
Pussy.
おまんこ
Rub it all over there.
そこいっぱいこすってほら
My fingers told me to hit it.
指がしぶつけろって
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
into the hole.
穴の中に
I'm pulling the strings.
糸ひいてるよ
Does it feel good?
上気持ちいいの?
気持ちいいの?
do not have.
ない
Kuru-chan, do you feel better?
くるちゃん、もっと上気持ちいいかほら
It feels good.
気持ちいいとこ
Kuru-chan.
くるちゃん
Let's use the secret station.
秘密駅使っちゃおう
Look, it's a shiny manju.
ほら、まんじゅるでテカテカだよ
Let's hit this on Kikuri.
これ、きくりに当てちゃおうよ
Can I use it?
使っていい?
It's a conversion.
変換なんだね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's no good, I'll move.
ダメじゃん、動いちゃう
I'm getting tired.
つれちゃうよ
It feels so good to be curly, isn't it?
くりぱんぱんで気持ちいいんでしょ
Let's get something out.
なんか出そう
Does something feel good come out?
くり気持ちよくなんか出ちゃうの?
Look, it's swollen.
ほ ら、腫れてるもんしてる
Are you going out?
出ちゃうの?
Kuru-chan, please tease me more.
くるちゃん、もっといじめてもらう
Your juices are swollen.
汁腫れてるよね
It feels so good that my juices come out.
気持ちよくて汁出ちゃうんだよ
Look, look.
ほ ら、ほら
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、 すごい
There are a lot of them.
いっぱい出てる
I don't have to finish it again.
もう一回、仕切れなくていい
Look, it's flying.
ほ ら、飛んでる
Wow, it's flying.
すごい、飛んでるよ
amazing.
すごい
Maybe I can't.
多分、できないんだ
Can you do it?
できちゃう?
amazing.
すごい
I'm putting it in.
入れてる
Very, very much.
めっちゃ、めっちゃ
Everyone looks cute.
みんな、かわいい顔してる
Everyone is putting out a lot.
みんな、いっぱい出してる
I'm putting it in.
入れてる
Look, there's a lot of it.
ほ ら、いっぱい出てる
amazing.
すごい
Wow, I can't stop.
うわ、止まんない
It's really stopped.
めっちゃ止まってる
amazing.
すごい
Wow, there's a lot out there, look.
すごい、いっぱい出てるね、ほら
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい
Let it fly.
飛ばしてね
That feels good.
それ、気持ちいいんだ
I can't stop now.
止まんなくなっちゃったね
Whatever you do, put this on.
これ、どうしようもつけてさ
Wait, let's go inside?
ちょっと、中入れちゃう?
Get me a drink.
お酒を飲んでもらって
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
A lot of this came out.
こんな、いっぱい出ちゃった
Did it come out comfortably?
気持ちよく出ちゃったの?
You held back.
我慢したのね
I couldn't do it.
できなかったんだ
Because it won't stop.
止まってくれないから
He wouldn't stop, so I came out.
止まってくれないから、出ちゃったんだ
It was very naughty though.
すごいエッチだったけどね
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
It's so small.
こんな、ちっちゃい
But can I do it?
でも、いけるかな?
tight?
きつい?
It's tough.
きついね
But I'm drinking it.
でも、飲み込んでる
I really got into it.
本当に、入っちゃった
I can see it myself.
見える、自分で
All of them are thick.
全部、太いところになっちゃってるから
Pry it away.
こじって、離して
Look.
見て
It stings.
刺さってるよ
amazing.
すごい
Small, cunt.
ちっちゃい、おまん
Does it feel good there?
そこ、気持ちいいの?
There were a lot of places that felt good.
気持ちいいところ、いっぱい出ちゃった
I say it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいって言うよ
You've come across a lot of places that feel good.
気持ちいいところ、いっぱい出ちゃったでしょ
At the top, at the top.
上のところ、上のところ
Let's take a look at it slowly.
ゆっくり見てみようか
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
Too small.
ちっちゃすぎる
Ah, I can go, I can go.
あ、いける、いける
It's spreading.
広がってる
It's easy, right?
簡単でしょ
簡 単でしょ
Can I use 2 new weapons?
新兵器、2使っていい?
Have you ever used a vibrator?
バイブ使ったことある?
It was a big shoot, wasn't it?
撮影でっかいやったよね?
It felt good, right?
気持ちよかったでしょ?
Put it in yourself.
自分でそれ入れてごらん
Can it fit this big?
こんなでっかい入るかな?
Small, cunt.
ちっちゃい、おまん
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだよ
There's a lot in it.
すごい入ってる
It's so soft.
ふっといね
Let me show you how perverted you are.
い っぱい変態なところ見せてもらお
cormorant.
う
Where does it feel good?
ど こが気持ちいいの?
At the top?
上のところ?
Let's open that up a lot.
そこ、いっぱい開かせてもらおう
It's included in the original.
一番のもとも入ってるじゃん
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Put something like this in it.
こんなふっといの入れて
That feels good.
そこが気持ちいいね
What do you like?
どうがいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
how was it?
どうだった?
Pussy.
おまんこ
I really wanted to.
めっちゃしたくなっちゃった
Give me your pussy.
おまんこして
Come here.
こっちおいでほら
Asaki-chan.
あさきちゃん
Look.
見て
It really came out.
めっちゃ出ちゃったね
I couldn't hold back my feelings.
気持ちの我慢できなかった
Kubo-chan, let's put this one in your pussy.
くぼちゃん、これにさ、 このいっちなまんこ入れちゃおうか
Asaki-chan, come here.
あさきちゃん、こっちきて
Let's roll over in bed.
ベッドね、転がっとくか
Soaked?
びしょびしょ?
I took off my skirt.
スカート抜いちゃったね
Manjulade is drenched.
マンジュレードびしょびしょになっちゃったね
Try it.
やってごらんぞ
Kubo-chan.
く ぼちゃん
I'm about to put my dick in your face and in your mouth.
もう、ちんちん顔に 口の中入れちゃう
Kubo-chan, please move more.
くぼちゃん、もっと動いてみ
Don't come.
くるしねぇ
Just push it harder.
もっと突っ込んでほら
Hey there.
ほ らほら
Come down.
下おいで
Let's put this in.
入 れちゃおうか、これ
Get it wet and fill it up.
濡らしていっぱい入れな
Look, there's a lot of mangel on it.
ほら、マンジュレいっぱいついてるよ
It's all in.
全部入っちゃった
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
My penis is sticking out from my mange.
マンジュレでてかってる、ちんちん
Ki-san.
きさん
Okay, go.
いい よ、いって
Look,
ほ ら、
It feels good, Kubo-chan.
気 持ちよくなんだよ、くぼちゃん
Follow me.
つ いて
I feel good.
気分いいです
Hit it all the way to the bottom.
一番奥までぶつかして
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's full of dicks.
ちんちんでいっぱいなっちゃったね
Aren't you going to leave?
いっちゃうんじゃないの?
Look, here you go.
見てごらん、ほら
It feels really good, Masaki-chan.
めっちゃ気持ちよさそうだね、まさきちゃん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Masaki-chan, please wake up next time.
まさきちゃん、今度起きてみ?
Wake up?
起きて?
Can you wake up?
起きれる?
Please be careful,
注意してごらん、
Look.
ほ ら
Come on, look.
ついて、ほら
Look where it's in.
入ってるところにしてごらん
Masaki-chan, shake your ass yourself.
まさきちゃん、自分でお尻振ってさ、
Here you go.
ちんちんほら
Follow me yourself.
ついてごらん、自分で
amazing.
すごい
Please put it all the way in.
一番奥まで入れてごらん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Shake your butt yourself.
自分でお尻振ってごらん
Just choreograph it.
まんま振り付けて
Wow, that's terrible.
すごい、やばい
It's all the way in, right?
奥まで入ってるでしょ?
painful.
苦しい
Is your penis painful?
ちんちんで苦しい?
Kuro-chan just followed me.
くろちゃん、そのままついてしたから
Follow me a lot.
い っぱいついて
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Kuro-chan, once again.
くろちゃん、もう一度
Try moving forward
前もっかってみ
hand.
て
Please be careful.
注意 してごらん
Leave it in.
入れたまま
Kuro-chan, take a look.
くろちゃん、むいてごらん
Chin chin.
ち んちん
Be careful.
注意しながら
Take it all out.
いっぱいぐる出して
Stand up more.
もっと立てて
It's all included.
全部入ってるよ
Even when I leave, I can see it completely.
離るも丸見え
Try to put on a pleasant face.
気持ちいい顔にしてごらん
Chin-chin, it feels good, right?
ちんちん、気持ちいいでしょ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'd like you to do some more perverted poses.
もっと変態のポーズしてもらおうかな
Kuro-chan, there you are.
くろちゃん、あった
This way.
こっち向き
Climb on top of this.
この上乗ってごらん
I'll put it in myself.
自分でちんちん入れるんだよ
backwards.
後ろ向きに
This way.
こっち向き
With a swirl, you see.
まんじれで、ほら
It's soaking wet.
びしょびしょいってる
Fidgety fidgety.
そわそわそわそわ
Try rolling it up a lot.
いっぱい巻いてごらん
It felt good.
気持ちよくしたね
It's stuck deep inside, you see.
ちばん奥まで刺さってるよ、ほら
Chiku also tried to be safe on top and was fine.
ちくさんも上で無事してみて、無事
Follow me with your hands behind me.
手後ろもついて
It stings.
刺さってる
Look at it a lot.
いっぱい見して
Lift your hips a little.
腰ちょっと浮かしてごらん
Lift your hips.
腰浮かして
Kuro-chan, hit me from below as hard as you can.
くろちゃん、下から思いっきりつく
More strictly.
もっと厳しく
Well then, Asahi-chan.
じゃあ、あさひちゃん
Stop with your hips lifted.
腰浮かしたままストップ
I hope you get tired of it there.
そこでいっぱいつかれてごらん
Kuro-chan, hurry up.
くろちゃん、もっと早く
Roll it up a lot.
いっぱい巻いて
Follow me.
ついて
Roll it all up into a circle.
全部丸く巻いてごらん
Follow me harder.
もっと激しくついてごらん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Just look at what she does with this naughty pose.
このエッチなポーズでいくとこ見してごらん
This is no good.
これダメ
I've been watching you for a long time, so here you go.
ずっと見てるから、ほら
I went again.
また行っちゃったんだ
Oh-kun, you're going to run into trouble.
おうくん、ひっくりひっくりしちゃうんじゃん
Hey, look this way.
ほら、こっち向いて
You can turn your head.
向いていいから
Hang in there.
よっつんばえして
It's fine facing this way.
こっち向きでいいよ
This way, this way.
こ っち向き、こっち向き
Look at this spirit with all your might.
この気をしりっぱい見して
Everything from the tip to the back.
先っぽから奥まで全部
Open your shoulders.
肩 を開きさして
Show me your pleasant face.
気持ちいい顔、こっち見せて
You're talking a lot.
くちくち言ってるね
Oh-kun,
おうくん、
Is it correct?
当 たってる?
That's right.
当たってる
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
There are a lot of them, right?
い っぱい付いてるでしょ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Look, there are a lot of them.
ほ ら、いっぱい付いてる
You can't go yet.
まだ行っちゃダメだよ
Just be patient.
我慢だよ
Don't come.
来ちゃダメだよ
Even if it's about to come, just hold on.
来そうになっても我慢だよ
Here, I'll put more.
ほら、もっと置く
Not yet.
まだダメ
Even if it feels good, be patient.
気持ちよくても我慢だよ
Raise it more.
もっと上げて
About oddities.
半端について
it hurts.
痛い
Just be patient.
我慢だよ
Did you cut your hand?
手を切っちゃったの?
I have a hand.
手を持ってる
It's fine to stay on the bottom in that state.
その状態で下についたままでいいから
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's all the way in, right?
奥まで全部入ってるでしょ?
It's in.
入ってる
I opened my shoulders.
肩を開けた
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Raise it more.
もっと上げて
Impossible.
無理
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Everything feels better now.
全部気持ちよくなっちゃってるね
I'll put it in.
入れちゃうよ
My penis is so big.
ちんちんすごいパンパンだよ
There are a lot of them.
い っぱいあって
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
You understand, right?
分かるでしょ?
My penis is getting big.
ちんちんでっかくなってる
Where should I get tired?
どこ疲れたらいい?
Deepest?
一番奥?
Do you like the back?
奥がいい?
I like the back.
奥がいい
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
I'll stick my mouth out as hard as I can.
口を思いっきり出しちゃう
Be patient and collect as much as you can.
我慢し、いっぱい溜めてからね
air
気
It lasts a long time.
持 ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
気 持 ちいい
Fill your tight pussy and see.
きついまんこいっぱい入れてほら
It's funny if you don't go
行かないとおもしろ
stomach.
い
Let's dig deeper.
も っと奥ついてもらおう
Because I have a penis in me.
ちんちん入れられてるから
Because we are very close.
い っぱ いあってるから
Can be used deep inside.
奥まで使える
Let's get to the bottom of it.
一番奥ついてもらおう
This feels good, right?
これ気持ちいいでしょ?
No.
ダメだよ
I have to be patient.
我慢しないと
No way, no way.
無理無理
It's really bad.
めっちゃダメだよ
Chin-chin, look.
ちんちん、ほら
I brought a lot of stuff.
しばんぱんぱん持ってきた
Be patient with me.
僕に我慢してよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Let's go, let's go.
行っちゃう、行っちゃう
Your mouth is full of paper.
口の中水紙だらけだね
Because the pussy I went to is awake.
行ったまんこ起きてるから
Wed: It turned out to be a mess.
水 紙まぎれになっちゃったね
Wake up.
起きてほら
It's become bushy.
ふさふさになっちゃったね
difficult.
難しい
I'll be back.
戻ってきます
I cleaned everything, but it got dirty with water paper.
全部きれいにしてあげて、水紙で汚くなっちゃった
Finally, just the tongue.
最後、ベロだけで
The whole thing is just the tongue.
ベロだけで全体
amazing.
すごい
I want to lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めたいな
Grow Jupojupo.
ジュポジュポ育てて
how was it?
どうだった?
Today is.
今日は
It was intense.
激しかった
激しかったね
It felt really good, didn't it?
めっちゃ気持ちよかったんじゃない?
today.
今日
I've been there a lot.
いっぱい行っちゃったもんね
It was gone except inside me.
僕の中以外行っちゃってた
It was so cute.
すごい可愛かったよ
Thank you.
ありがとうね
Let's play again.
また遊ぼうよ
I'll go again.
また行っちゃいますよ
Don't tell everyone.
みんなに内緒にね
Well then, thank you.
じゃあ、ありがとうね
I'll do it again.
またしちゃう
bye bye.
バイバイ